livingexclusive.com.au 2017-02-15

# Brands Exclusive - Privacy Policy

## Privacy Policy

### Disclaimer

Welcome to brandsExclusive.com.au (the “Website”). This Website is owned and operated by Brands Exclusive (Australia) pty ltd (collectively, "Brands Exclusive", "we", or "us" or “our”). Brands Exclusive is sensitive to your concerns about how we may use and share personal information that we collect from you through the Website.

We are committed to providing our members with the best possible products and services. This requires that we store and use from time to time your private information such as name, address, contact number and email address. We also want our members and business partners to have the confidence that we manage their personal information with an appropriate and legally required level of privacy.

This Privacy Policy covers the Website as well as information provided through any means of communication to Brands Exclusive. In this privacy policy, “you” and “your” and other similar references mean a specific user of the Website and the members and members of Brands Exclusive. By visiting the Websites and or by becoming a member you accept the practices described in this Privacy Policy.

### Gathering of Personal Information

Personal Information is any information that identifies you, would enable someone to contact you, or that describes your relationship with Brands Exclusive. We collect and store Personal Information you enter on our Website or give in any other way (e.g. by telephone). This may include information you provide when you become a member and/or login to use our Websites, ask a question, complete a form, conduct a transaction, or send us an email. Member account information will be collected and may be made available on the Website for ease of use and enabling single member accounts.

While you are not required to submit any information to our Website, if you do not provide the requested information, you may not be able to access or use some of the features and functions of our Websites and we may not be able to provide you with certain services.

Brands Exclusive uses your Personal Information to complete transactions, respond to your questions and requests, deliver the products and services you purchased or requested (Please note that this may include providing your Personal Information to third parties to enable the delivery of products and services which you purchased or requested or for related Brands Exclusive marketing purposes) and to notify you of upcoming sales events and promotions, updates, or special offers that we think may interest you.

Brands Exclusive does not intentionally gather data from or about children. Minors are not permitted to participate in Brands Exclusive Sales.

In the event that brandsExclusive.com.au, all or substantially all of their respective assets, or a line of business of brandsExclusive.com.au is acquired, individually identifying information of our members may be one of the assets sold in connection with that transaction, without notice to you or your consent. We will notify users of the Website of such a change in ownership or transfer of assets by posting a notice on the Website.

Some of the information that is collected on our Website is not Personal Information, because it does not reveal your identity. For example, we may record your server address, domain name, the date and time of your visit to this site and the pages that you viewed. This information is used by us in anonymous, aggregated form only, for statistical and Website development purposes.

However, we reserve the right to use or disclose this information to try to locate an individual if we reasonably believe that the individual may have engaged in any unlawful or inappropriate activity in connection with our Website.

A cookie is a small data file that a website transfers to your Internet browser for identification purposes. The cookies that we use do not identify you individually. Instead, they identify your Internet browser.

We use “session” cookies to maintain session information about you when you log into our Website, which enables us to personalise your current visit and perform ecommerce activities such as maintaining your shopping basket.

We also use “persistent” cookies to personalise the user experience, to help protect our members and to provide us with user information of our Website. Persistent cookies allow us to track users on our Website and help us identify users abusing our service.

Most Internet browsers are set to accept cookies. If you prefer not to receive them, you can adjust your browser to reject cookies, or to notify you when they are being used. There are also software products available that can manage cookies for you. Rejecting cookies can however limit the functionality of our Website.

We use Google Analytics (a web analytics services provided by Google) and data such as age, gender and browsing activity to better understand the behaviour of our customers and provide targeted advertising to suit customers interests and preferences. Accordingly, when you visit our website, we, and/or a third party, may place cookies on your browser to determine information including (but not limited to) your computers location, browsing activity and time spent on each web page. We and/or Google may use this information to optimise and place advertisements. By using this website and agreeing to this policy, you grant us permission to place and store cookies on your browser. Cookies can be managed by accessing the individual settings in your browser.

### Access to Information

Brands Exclusive has implemented a range of safeguards in an attempt to prevent unauthorised access, maintain your data and correctly use your personal information through technological, physical and administrative measures.

As specified in this privacy policy and as much as commercially reasonable, we limit access to your personal information. However, employees, officers and appointed business partners will need your personal information to perform their role in providing you our products and services.

We may provide aggregate statistics about our members, sales, traffic patterns and related site information to our supply partners or third party vendors, but these statistics do not include Personal Information.

We do not share information with third parties for their direct marketing purposes.

In providing our members and members with products or services, we may disclose personal information to third parties. This includes companies that perform marketing services and other business operations and services for us or supply products to us.

In the case of contracted service providers, we may disclose Personal Information to the contracted service provider and the contracted service provider may in turn provide us with Personal Information collected from you in the course of providing the relevant products or services. We take steps to help ensure that our contracted service providers comply with the National Privacy Principles when they collect and handle your Personal Information.

We may also disclose personal information to third parties:

• where required or authorised by or under law to do so; and/or

• with your consent (which may be written, verbal or implied from your conduct).

We may also disclose Personal Information in the good-faith belief that disclosure is necessary to protect and defend our rights or property or the rights or property of other users of our Website, or to act in an emergency to protect the personal safety of users of our Website or the public.

### External Links

Other companies or organisations may have links to their website on our Website. Brands Exclusive is not responsible for how these other companies or organisations collect, use, disclose, or secure the information that you provide them. If you choose to access a third party website linked to our Website, you do so at your own risk and subject to any terms of service or privacy policy (if any) associated with such third party website.

### Changes to Personal Data

You can view and change your Personal Information we have stored in the "My Account" area on the website.

### Unsubscribe or Membership Cancellation

We will send you emails for new sales events, promotions, special offers, reminders, contests and marketing promotions. Such emails may include marketing information about brandsExclusive.com.au or selected business partners. If you wish to unsubscribe, please go to the My Account section on each Website and update your email preferences. In addition, each email we send will contain an easy automated unsubscribe link so that you can opt-out of that subscription.

If you wish to cancel your membership and have your Personal Information removed from our database for any reason, simply contact us via the "Contact Us" page or email us at [support@brandsexclusive.com.au](mailto:support@brandsexclusive.com.au)

### Modification and Notification of Changes

Brands Exclusive may at our sole discretion edit this Privacy Policy because of changes in Internet technology or applicable legislation. Please ensure you check this Privacy Policy from time to time for such changes.

### Complaints, Questions or Suggestions about your Privacy

If you have questions or suggestions regarding this Privacy Policy or our privacy practices please contact us via the “Support” section on our Website.

Any complaints in relation to your privacy may be directed to The Privacy officer at [support@brandsexclusive.com.au](mailto:support@brandsexclusive.com.au) or by letter to Brands Exclusive (Australia) pty ltd,

Level 12, 201 Kent St, Sydney NSW 2000
